Contact

shahirzain100@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/shahirzain (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Python (Programming Language)

R

Data Science

Languages

Urdu (Native or Bilingual)

English (Professional Working)

Certifications

Build Your Own Chatbot - Level 1

Learning Chrome Web Developer Tools

Microsoft Office Specialist Excel 2016

Blockchain Basics

Introduction to Python

Shahir Zain

Solidity & Javascript Developer - Front & Back End - Experienced Karāchi

Summary

Technology Enthusiast, experienced in Web Apps, Computer Vision and Databases Handling. I did freelancing in Computer Vision and Al I have great experiences in cutting edge technologies such as

Mern Stack technology

ReactJs

Redux

React Query

Gatsbyjs

Nodejs

MongoDB

Express

GraphQL

jest

react-testing-library

cypress

Al Technologies

Python

Numpy

Pandas

Matplotlib

Seaborn

Keras

Pytorch

OpenCv

Dlib

I have also experience with various tools and task runners like

Npm

Git

Besides that, I have done Bachelors in Computer Science from Federal Urdu University Arts Science and Technology.

To be a Full Stack Engineer, I love development, love to play with 'Cutting Edge Technologies, and pleased to be a part of the development team

Experience

Nisum

1 year 4 months

Software Engineer - JavaScript April 2021 - Present (1 year) Karāchi, Sindh, Pakistan

Software Engineer Intern
December 2020 - March 2021 (4 months)

Karachi Division, Pakistan

Fiverr

Freelance Developer September 2020 - August 2021 (1 year)

I am providing services of Machine Learning and Data Science

Daraz

Seller

August 2019 - January 2021 (1 year 6 months)

Karāchi, Sindh, Pakistan

i work on Daraz on my leisure hours i sell many product , due to E-commerce revolution i can generate enough pocket money

Education

Federal Urdu University of Arts, Science & Technology, Islamabad. Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Science · (2017 - 2020)

Udacity

Nano Degree, Computer Vision · (2020 - 2020)

365DataScience

Deep Learning with Tensorflow, Deep Learning · (2020 - 2020)